malayalamlive.com 2018-10-03

# MalayalamLive.com - Privacy Policy

Last Updated on 04/11/2009 

This document sets forth the Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this Web site, www.malayalamlive.com (the "Site"). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or other web sites related to malayalamlive.com.

**Changes in Privacy Policy**  
All "personal information" ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to the version of the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of such collection. malayalamlive.com reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion, and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. 

**Entities collecting personal information**  
The Site collects personal information such as email address, which we will store in our system. The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.

**Collection of personal information**  
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. When you submit personal information to malayalamlive.com through this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which malayalamlive.com and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including, without limitation, the United States. 

malayalamlive.com collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. malayalamlive.com will NOT by any chance share any such personal information with any 3rd parties. We may use the personal information such as email for communications and newsletters.

malayalamlive.com may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. malayalamlive.com may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

Also, please note that malayalamlive.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any other Web sites to which this Site may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.

**Thanks for visiting malayalamlive.com!**
